Guide to the Susie Bright papers and On Our Backs records, 1978-2013.
Bright, Susie papers and On Our Backs records
- Series III. Writings
  - Media Books
    - Sexfantasyzone.com: Best American Erotica 2001 review, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 219)
    - Susie Bright media raves (Box 19, Folder 220)
    - Susie Bright book, lecture, film reviews (Box 19, Folder 221)
    - Susie Bright face time (Box 19, Folder 222)
  - Salon Magazine: Sexpert Opinion by Susie Bright
    - Lilith vs. Dyke-o-rama: No contest, July 18, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 223)
    - Everyone's a Porn Star, August 1, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 224)
    - Why I Should Use My Vibrator More Often, September 2, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 225)
    - From Generation Excess to Generation Sexless, October 10, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 226)
    - Why Johnny (and Janine) Can't Get It On, November 7, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 227)
    - You're Not Crazy, It's Just Christmas, December 19, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 228)
    - Busting Out, January 16, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 229)
    - Backdoor Mania, February 27, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 230)
    - Porn 101, April 10, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 231)
    - Porn to be Bad: Teaching Colelge Students About the Dark Side of Sex, April 24, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 232)
    - Move Over, Ken, It's "Bend Over Boyfriend", May 22, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 233)
    - Abstinence Blues: Teen Sex Isn't Always Traumatic, June 19, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 234)
    - Viagra Calls, II: Curse of the Trophy Wives, July 31, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 235)
    - Sexpert Sale, September 11, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 236)
    - Erotic Wasteland, March 5, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 237)
    - Shave the World, March 19, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 238)
    - Fallen Angels, May 15, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 239)
    - Don't Be Sore, August 7, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 240)
    - Herpes Nation, August 21, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 241)
    - Sexpert Opinion, June 1997 - May 1999 (Box 19)
      For Salon Magazine, Susie's final copies.
- Counter Visions
  Submissions for Counter Visions photography project.
  - Helen Keller (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Kelso (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Gloria Karlson (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Triplett, September 19, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Geist, December 1982 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Mary Beth Edelson, January 9, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - C. Elliot (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Cathy Cade (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Karby (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Leslie Starobin (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Kathy Morris (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Ronnie Hartman and Lora Gordan (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Craigie Houston (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Jeb (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Cheryl Sena (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Barbara Hammer/Garside (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Morgan Gwenwald (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Linda Parks (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Jan Phillips (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - O'Shea (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Renee Jones (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Mountaingrove (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Carol Newhouse (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Catalina Gorea (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Nadine Minces. Baron (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Carol Hoffman (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Olson (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - CounterVision (Misc.) (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Lorain Meyers and Elen Meyers (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Marta Huante (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Sarah Vogwill (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Diana Duff (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Mary Taylor (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Judith Ronay (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Tea for Two Shirts (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Smokey Cormier (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Misc. (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - Belle Brett (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - M. Boutin (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - Carol Spindel (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - Diana Duff (Box 13, Folder 41)
  - Carrie Mae Weems (Box 13, Folder 42)
  - Wozin (Box 13, Folder 43)
  - Heidi Rand (Box 13, Folder 44)
  - Donna Ann McAdams (Box 13, Folder 45)
  - Suzanne Williamson (Box 13, Folder 46)
  - Jo Anne Obermaier (Box 13, Folder 47)
  - Judy Janda (Box 13, Folder 48)
  - O'Neill (Box 13, Folder 49)
  - Patt Mruray/Molly (Box 13, Folder 50)
  - Erica Marcus (Box 13, Folder 51)
  - Jane Lurie (Box 13, Folder 52)
  - Irene Kane (Box 13, Folder 53)
  - Chris Kage Lius (Box 13, Folder 54)
  - Jo Ellen Arnold (Box 13, Folder 55)
  - Agapito (Box 13, Folder 56)
  - Janice Baker (Box 13, Folder 57)
  - Debbie Hoffman (Box 13, Folder 58)
  - Virginia Harris (Box 13, Folder 59)
  - Shoshana (Box 13, Folder 60)
  - Majak Bredwell (Box 13, Folder 61)
  - L.C. Faye (Box 13, Folder 62)
  - Zand Gee (Box 13, Folder 63)
  - Tracewell (Box 13, Folder 64)
  - Honey Lee Cottrell (Box 13, Folder 65)
  - Wolstoncraft (Box 13, Folder 66)
  - Karen E. Johnson (Box 13, Folder 67)
  - Ruth Morgan (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Barbara Klutinis (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Non-Traditional (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Zoe Mosko (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - L.A. Hyder (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Jane Gibbons/Nancy Huebble (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - J. Baker (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Frances Hee (Box 14, Folder 8)
- On Our Backs
  Documents relating to On Our Backs magazine. Issues of the publication; various files pertaining to the business of producing OOB, as well as the Stormy Leather catalog, the OOB 1989 Lesbian Sex Calendar and Fatale Video; and articles that account for the critical and popular reception of OOB as well as OOB’s contribution to the Sexual Revolution and Feminist Porn Wars. Personal photographs, letters, papers and works of and by the OOB staff document the lives of the women behind the magazine and their experience working for OOB and attending OOB related events. Also included is a collection of slides from pornographic films.
  - On Our Backs Issues
    - Volume 1, Issue 1, Summer 1984 (Box 21)
    - Volume 1, Issue 2, Fall 1984 (Box 21)
    - Volume 1, Issue 3, Winter 1985 (Box 21)
    - Volume 1, Issue 4, Spring 1985 (Box 21)
    - Volume 2, Issue 1, Summer 1985 (Box 21)
    - Volume 2, Issue 2, Fall 1985 (Box 21)
    - Volume 2, Issue 3, Winter 1986 (Box 21)
      Published without a volume or issue number.
    - Volume 2, Issue 4, Spring 1986 (Box 21)
    - Volume 2, Issue 5, Summer 1986 (Box 21)
      This issue should have been numbered Volume 3, Issue 1, as such no issue was published as Volume 3, Issue 1.
    - Volume 3, Issue 2, Fall 1986 (Box 21)
    - Volume 3, Issue 3, Winter 1987 (Box 21)
    - Volume 3, Issue 4, Spring 1987 (Box 21)
    - Volume 4, Issue 1, Summer 1987 (Box 21)
    - Volume 4, Issue 2, Fall 1987 (Box 21)
    - Volume 4, Issue 3, Winter 1988 (Box 21)
    - Volume 4, Issue 4, Spring 1988 (Box 21)
    - Volume 5, Issue 1, Summer 1988 (Box 21)
    - Volume 5, Issue 2, Fall 1988 (Box 21)
    - Volume 5, Issue 3, January - February 1989 (Box 21)
    - Volume 5, Issue 4, March - April 1989 (Box 21)
    - Volume 5, Issue 5, May - June 1989 (Box 21)
    - Volume 5, Issue 6, July - August 1989 (Box 21)
    - Volume 6, Issue 1, September - October 1989 (Box 21)
    - Volume 6, Issue 2, November - December 1989 (Box 21)
    - Volume 6, Issue 3, January - February 1990 (Box 21)
    - Volume 6, Issue 4, March - April 1990 (Box 21)
    - Volume 6, Issue 5, May - June 1990 (Box 21)
    - Volume 6, Issue 6, July - August 1990 (Box 21)
    - Volume 7, Issue 1, September - October 1990 (Box 21)
    - Volume 7, Issue 2, November - December 1990 (Box 21)
      Published as Volume 7, Issue 1, repeating previous.
    - Volume 7, Issue 3, January - February 1991 (Box 21)
    - Volume 7, Issue 4, March - April 1991 (Box 21)
    - Volume 7, Issue 5, May - June 1991 (Box 21)
    - Volume 7, Issue 6, July - August 1991 (Box 21)
    - Volume 8, Issue 1, September - October 1991 (Box 21)
    - Volume 8, Issue 2, November - December 1991 (Box 21)
    - Volume 8, Issue 3, January - February 1992 (Box 21)
    - Volume 8, Issue 4, March - April 1992 (Box 21)
    - Volume 8, Issue 5, May - June 1992 (Box 21)
    - Volume 8, Issue 6, July - August 1992 (Box 21)
    - Volume 9, Issue 1, September - October 1992 (Box 21)
    - Volume 9, Issue 2, November - December 1992 (Box 21)
    - Volume 9, Issue 3, January - February 1993 (Box 21)
    - Volume 9, Issue 4, March - April 1993 (Box 21)
    - Volume 9, Issue 5, May - June 1993 (Box 21)
    - Volume 9, Issue 6, July - August 1993 (Box 21)
    - Volume 10, Issue 1, September - October 1993 (Box 21)
    - Volume 10, Issue 2, November - December 1993 (Box 21)
    - Volume 10, Issue 3, January - February 1994 (Box 21)
    - Volume 10, Issue 4, March - April 1994 (Box 21)
    - Volume 10, Issue 5, May - June 1994 (Box 21)
    - Volume 10, Issue 6, July - August 1994 (Box 21)
    - Volume 11, Issue 1, September - October 1994 (Box 21)
    - Volume 11, Issue 1, January - February 1995 (Box 21)
      Published as Volume 11, Issue 1, repeating previous.
    - Duplicate set of "On Our Backs" for scanning project - not for patron use, 1989-1995; RESTRICTED (Box 25)
  - Administrative Files
    - OOB Staff Photoshoot (Box 13, Folder 68)
    - Erotica Prints, 1985-1989 (Box 13, Folder 69)
    - Portraits of Unknown Models (Box 13, Folder 70)
    - Cards and Photographs (Box 13, Folder 71)
      Includes small Susie Bright business card with a color photograph of a young Susie Bright on the back, wearing a zippered black teddy and long leather gloves from her cameo in the movie Bound.
    - OOB Bookstore Order Form, January 10, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 72)
    - OOB 5 year Anniversary Endorsements, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 76)
    - Noreen Scully Original Drawing, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 77)
    - OOB Emergency Fund Donation, May 30, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 78)
    - Other Lesbian Establishment Contacts (Box 13, Folder 80)
    - OOB Review by Dorothy Allison (Box 13, Folder 85)
    - Stormy Leather catalogue (Box 13, Folder 94)
    - OOB 1989 Lesbian Sex Calendar, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 96)
    - Stormy Leather photos (Box 13, Folder 102)
    - OOB Photo Edits (Box 13, Folder 104)
    - Honey Lee Cotrell letterhead (Box 13, Folder 109)
    - On Our Backs--Media (Sojourner, Rag Times, OUT Week, etc.) (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Originals--Samois Newsletter, 1982-1983 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Lesbian Nation Article, March 2, 2009 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Debi Resume (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Butch/Femme Drafter, Debi S. (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - "My Work in the Sex Industry"--Deborah Willenbring/Debi Sundahl, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - OOB Pat and Joe's Farewell Dinner (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Letters to Debi (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - "My Work in the Sex Industry", 1983 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Femme Article (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - OOB Notes/Schedule (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Draft Unknown Piece (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Rental Agreement and Bills (Nan and Debi), 1980-1983 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Sexual Satisfaction Draft (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Letter to Madeline from Debi: Butch/Fem Dynamics (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - OOB Sexual Assault (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - Debi--List of Speaking Engagements (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Personal Letters (Nancy, Debi, Johnny, Family) (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - Stonepeg Productions Application: Debi, May 19, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - Debi Notebook/Journal (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - Nan and Blaise Hit the Open Road, November 27, 1993 (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - Battle Scars By Debi Sundahl (Box 23, Folder 22)
    - Newspaper Clipplings/Notes (Box 23, Folder 23)
    - "A Woman's Place" By Gayle Rubin, September 7, 1984 (Box 23, Folder 24)
    - "Pro Sex Feminist" notes (Box 23, Folder 25)
    - Business Plan/Banking (Box 23, Folder 26)
    - Editor-In-Chief Notes, 1991-1992 (Box 23, Folder 27)
    - Tax Returns, 1985-1993 (Box 23, Folder 28)
    - Lesbian/Porn/Antiporn News Clippings, 1981-1993 (Box 23, Folder 29)
    - "Porn, Sexuality and Difference", December 17, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 30)
    - Women's News Correspondence, 1984 (Box 23, Folder 31)
    - "Gay" Publication Correspondence (Box 23, Folder 32)
    - Journal "to be typed" (Box 23, Folder 33)
    - Budget Annuals, 6 Month and Annual, 1993-1994 (Box 23, Folder 34)
    - Rolodex #15 (Box 23, Folder 35)
    - Critical Payables, 1994 (Box 23, Folder 36)
    - Blush Customer List, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 37)
    - Staff Meeting, Hours, Contact, Office Notes (Box 23, Folder 38)
    - Blush Customer List, September 1994 (Box 23, Folder 39)
    - Sale Plan/Draft OOB (Box 23, Folder 40)
    - Letters to Deb, Nan, Susie--Fatale, 1983-1986 (Box 23, Folder 41)
    - To: Correspondence, From: Debi, 1982-1986, 1994 (Box 23, Folder 42)
      Includes letter to the producers of Cupido magazine asking to discuss producing an American edition.
    - OOB Features, Battle Scars (Box 23, Folder 43)
    - Going out of Business Plan, 1990-1994 (Box 23, Folder 44)
    - OOB Opperations Manual/Employee Communication (Box 23, Folder 45)
    - Correspondence Old Eagle Theater/Sacramento, 1986 (Box 23, Folder 46)
    - "Lesbian Strippers", 1986 (Box 23, Folder 47)
    - The Erotic Screen--Susie (Box 23, Folder 48)
    - Butch/Femme Connected Underneath, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 49)
    - OOB Forum, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 50)
    - Original Copies of Debi Sundahl's Articles (Box 23, Folder 51)
    - Fatale Correspondence, 1994 (Box 23, Folder 52)
    - Discovery Center--Fanny Fatale, 1996-1997 (Box 23, Folder 53)
    - Feminine Connections Newsletter, December 1985 (Box 23, Folder 54)
    - International Gay and Lesbian Archives (Box 23, Folder 55)
    - Volunteers, 1984-1985 (Box 23, Folder 56)
    - Advertisements/Flyers (Box 23, Folder 57)
    - OOB Memos--Meeting Minutes, 1994 (Box 23, Folder 58)
    - Pat Califa, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 59)
    - Sex Institue Dec. 8 (Box 23, Folder 60)
    - Chuck Winter--Playboy, 1984-1987 (Box 23, Folder 61)
    - Hooters Convention Speech, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 62)
    - Debi Articles (Box 23, Folder 63)
    - Article in Progress (Box 23, Folder 64)
    - Mitchell Brothers (Box 23, Folder 65)
    - National Leather Association/Ms. International Leather, 1987 (Box 23, Folder 66)
    - Monika Treut, 1985-1987 (Box 23, Folder 67)
    - Debi--University of Minnesota (Box 23, Folder 68)
    - Personal Letters to Debi, 1985-1987 (Box 23, Folder 69)
    - Fem/Lesbian News (Box 23, Folder 70)
    - Ask Fanny (Box 23, Folder 71)
    - Off Our Backs, 1986 (Box 23, Folder 72)
    - Colliers Erotic Reader, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 73)
    - Cards (Box 23, Folder 74)
    - OOB Covers, 1985-1995 (Box 23, Folder 75)
    - Nothing But the Girl, 1994 (Box 23, Folder 76)
    - Vibrators "R" Us and The Erotic Screen (Box 23, Folder 77)
    - Video Covers (Box 23, Folder 78)
    - New York Times Article, July 30, 1989 (Box 23, Folder 79)
    - Penthouse/Debi (Box 23, Folder 80)
    - L.A. Times (Box 23, Folder 81)
    - Strip Class Students (Box 23, Folder 82)
    - Fanny Letterhead, Bio, etc. (Box 23, Folder 83)
    - OOB Media Reviews (Box 23, Folder 84)
    - Contributor Contracts, 1985-1991 (Box 23, Folder 85)
  - On Our Backs Media
    - Interview of Susie Bright by Michael Evans, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 73)
    - Interview with Debi Sundahl and Susie Bright by Camilla Decarnin, August 20, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 74)
    - Fatale Video "Clips" Newspaper Advertisement, August 5, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 75)
    - Fatale Film Reviews, 1985-1990 (Box 13, Folder 79)
    - OOB Publicity Advertisements (Box 13, Folder 81)
    - "Working Woman" by Francine Brown-Article featured in San Jose Mercury News about Fanny Fatale, May 24, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 82)
    - Article about Jill Posener-"Passionately Political Lesbian Photography" by Noreen C. Barnes (Box 13, Folder 83)
    - Mercury News Photos of Susie Bright (Box 13, Folder 86)
    - "On Our Backs Vandalized" by Lisa Troshinsky, March 23, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 87)
    - "Lesbians Urge 'Safe Sex' as Aids Precaution" Featuring Susie Bright, December 30, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 88)
    - Articles Quoting Susie Bright, 1989-1990 (Box 13, Folder 89)
    - Letters to the Editor about OOB, 1985-1989 (Box 13, Folder 90)
    - Playboy Article about Susie Bright (Box 13, Folder 91)
    - The Chronicle article about Susie Bright by Alice Kahn (Box 13, Folder 92)
    - The New York Native article by Susie Bright, July 1984 (Box 13, Folder 93)
    - OOB 1989 Lesbian Sex Calendar articles, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 95)
    - "Nasty Girls" article in Mother Jones featuring Candida Royalle, OOB, Annie Sprinkle (Box 13, Folder 97)
    - Off Our Backs-Feminists and the Conflict over Pornography, June 1985 (Box 13, Folder 98)
    - "Andrea Dworkin talks Feminism and Pornography" in Gay Community news, December 1985 (Box 13, Folder 99)
    - Letter from Brenda Marston-HSC Curator, July 1985 (Box 13, Folder 100)
    - Off Our Backs Review of OOB by Denise Kulp, July 1985 (Box 13, Folder 101)
    - Newspaper Clippings of OOB, 1984-1990 (Box 13, Folder 105)
      Includes November 16, 1989 article from the San Francisco Examiner by Rob Morse mentioning Susie Bright's pregnancy.
    - Featured OOB Articles, 1984-1990 (Box 13, Folder 106)
    - OOB Reviews, 1984-1989 (Box 13, Folder 107)
    - Anti-Pornography Debate in the News, 1984-1987 (Box 13, Folder 109)
    - German Magazine article about OOB, July 1985 (Box 13, Folder 110)
    - Erotica Newspaper Clipping by Armistead Maupin in Halcyon Hill (Box 13, Folder 116)
  - On Our Backs Photos and Miscellaneous
    - On Our Backs Lesbian Calendar, 1989 (Box 21)
    - "Feeling the Heat" fundraiser performance featuring Susie Bright and Debi Sundahl, February 27, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 84)
    - "OOB Days" (Box 13, Folder 103)
    - Susie Bright fun photographs, Includes a small business card illustrated with a color photo of Susie Bright wearing a zippered black teddy and long leather gloves (Box 13, Folder 111)
    - Susie Bright at late night events (Box 13, Folder 112)
    - Miscellaneous Photoshoots (Box 13, Folder 113)
    - Susie Bright nude headshots (Box 13, Folder 114)
    - "Virgin Machine" Review, December 1989 (Box 13, Folder 115)
    - Different hairstyles-Susie Bright (Box 13, Folder 117)
    - Della Grace (Del LaGrace) Photoshoot with Susie Bright (Box 13, Folder 118)
    - Susie Bright American Flag photoshoot (Box 13, Folder 119)
    - Esquire Photoshoot-Susie Bright (Box 13, Folder 120)
    - Newsweek photoshoot with Susie Bright (Box 13, Folder 121)
    - Jill Posener Photoshoots with Susie Bright (Box 13, Folder 122)
    - "Bunny"-Photo Collage (Box 13, Folder 123)
    - Nothing But the Girl: The Blatant Lesbian Image by Susie Bright and Jill Posener, 1989-1990 (Box 13, Folder 124)
    - Michael Rosen photoshoot with Susie Bright (Box 13, Folder 125)
    - Phyllis Christopher photoshoot with Susie Bright (Box 13, Folder 126)
    - Annie Sprinkle Photoshoot with Susie Bright, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 127)
    - Photos of Susie Bright by various artists (Box 13, Folder 128)
    - Susie Bright Photo by Monika Treut on the set of "Virgin Machine" (Box 13, Folder 129)
    - Susie Bright portrait by Della Grace (Del LaGrace) (Box 13, Folder 130)
    - Book Tour-Susie Sexpert's Lesbian Sex World (Box 13, Folder 131)
    - "The Rainbow of Her Seasons: Six Feet Under", 2005 (Box 13, Folder 132)
    - "Virgin Machine", 1988 (Box 13, Folder 133)
    - "Celluloid Closet", 1995 (Box 13, Folder 134)
    - "Erotique", 1994 (Box 13, Folder 135)
    - Susie Bright speaks at Books and Co., NYC, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 136)
    - "Bound", 1994, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 137)
      Includes original script of the Larry and Andy Wachowski movie.
    - Susie Bright Photoshoot (Box 13, Folder 138)
    - Trip to see "How to Read a Dirty Movie" showing (Box 13, Folder 139)
      Also includes cue script and performance agreement.
    - Photographs by Honey Lee Cottrell (Box 13, Folder 140)
      Includes "Susie pregnant," "Just Squeezed" (grapefruit photo), "Voyeur eating popcorn."
    - Susie Personal photos (Box 13, Folder 141)
      Includes matted photo signed by Mark I Chester; a card from Honey Lee; a birthday card to Susie on her 33rd birthday; a photo by Rink from the San Francisco Pride parade 1984, "Just Laid"; a photo of Susie Bright wearing an Eveready shirt on a beach.
    - Poster of a Dildo (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Portrait of Susie Bright by Michael Rosen, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - July 1984 OOB Cover Photo-Original Photography, July 1984 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Photograph by Suskin (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Formerly framed cover of On Our Backs Ten Year Anniversary expanded issue; featuring Debi Sundahl, September/October 1984 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Debi Sundahl Burlezk Live slides, by Robert Altman-H.L., September 1984 (Box 24, Folder 1)
      Negatives of a hotel, also photos of Debi Sundahl posing with croquet stick and ball and an additional photo of Debi stripping.
      Annotation by Susie: Debi was a highly regarded dancer/stripper and often did public exhibitions for publicity.
    - Debi Sundahl interview at KFRC Radio slides., September 1984 (Box 24, Folder 2)
      20 color slides of Debi by an unknown commercial male photographer from an interview at radio station KFRC, San Francisco California.
      Annotation by Susie: Debi believes that this was one of the many "debates" we did on radio whether women’s performance was "good" or "bad" for women.
    - Bi-Costal slides., September 1984 (Box 24, Folder 3)
      Two publicity stills from the video Bi-Costal, first bisexual adult video in the 80s. Directed by Tom DiSomone. Cara Lott is one of the models.
      Annotation by Susie: First 2 men, 1 women XXX film ever produced by the mainstream porn industry. The director was a straight liberal who wanted "everyone to get along". It was not commercially successful at the time because of the straight audience, but a lot of gay men bought it.
    - "Exposure" (Box 24, Folder 4)
      slides
    - "Only the Strong Survive" (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - "Easy Access" (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - "Traci, I Love You" (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - "Western Trip", April 1980 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - "Snatched to the Future"-Elegant Angel (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - "Moonlusting" (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - "Samantha, I Love You" (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - "Satin Angels" (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - "Rock-N-Roll Heaven" (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - "Biloxi Babes" (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - "Portrait of an Affair" (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - "Unveiled" (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - "Hot Wired" (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - "Little Shop of Horrors" (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - "Blue Ecstacy" (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - "Brat" (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - "Revenge of the Babes" (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - "Cheating", 1987 (Box 24, Folder 22)
      slides, SEVP
    - "Ginger and Spice" (Box 24, Folder 23)
    - "Strip Search", 1987 (Box 24, Folder 24)
    - "In a Crystal Fantasy", 1988 (Box 24, Folder 25)
    - "Rites of Passion" (Box 24, Folder 26)
      slides, Jeanna Fine, David Sandler, Rodger T. Dodger, Annie Candida, Nina Hartley, Scott Baker, R. Bullock
    - Excalibur Films (Box 24, Folder 27)
    - "Outrageous Foreplay" (Box 24, Folder 28)
    - "Obsessed" (Box 24, Folder 29)
    - "Sinset Blvd." (Box 24, Folder 30)
    - "Sex Aliens" (Box 24, Folder 31)
    - "Little Miss Innocence" (Box 24, Folder 32)
    - "Hot Gun" (Box 24, Folder 33)
    - "Kiss of the Gypsy" (Box 24, Folder 34)
    - "The Bride" (Box 24, Folder 35)
    - "Between the Sheets" and "Careful He May Be Watching" (Box 24, Folder 36)
    - "Backside to the Future II" (Box 24, Folder 37)
    - "Three Daughters"-Femme Dist. Inc. (Box 24, Folder 38)
    - "Smoker" and "Les Be Friends" (Box 24, Folder 39)
    - Interracial Tapes (Box 24, Folder 40)
      "Passion Within" with Nina Hartley and John Leslie; "Black Lava" Wet Video, Jeannie Pepper; "Black Bun Busters", Wet Video of VCA, Sahara; "Let Me Tell You 'Bout Black Chicks" VCA
    - "My Masters"-Christopher Rage (Box 24, Folder 41)
    - "CaREENA 2" (Box 24, Folder 42)
    - "Black Moon Rising" (Box 24, Folder 43)
    - "Sexcape" (Box 24, Folder 44)
    - "Ubancis on Uranus" (Box 24, Folder 45)
    - St. X-Where II (Box 24, Folder 46)
    - Unknown Slides (Box 24, Folder 47)